that we have with us today, Pastor Joe and I are from the, well, he's retired now, congratulations to you.
He's going to give us our invocation.
Let's pray to get him, precious father.
Holy Savior, thank you, Father, for the privilege of being here tonight.
Thank you, Father, for each of these that are gathered here, especially Father,
these who have given up their time and their talents, their experience, their wisdom,
in leading and providing for the people of his city.
I pray, Father, that you give them wisdom and understanding, courage and strength for the task that is theirs.
I pray that everything they do and say, Father, will be according to your will and for the benefit of people.
Let's our country, thank you, Father, for our nation.
That still is in trouble, but still a nation that believes in you.
And all I pray, that you will guide our leaders.
I pray, Father, for our military, for our police, our fire workers, our first responders, our medical personnel.
I pray, Father, for all those who have a ministry to others.
Now, Father, I ask that to deliveration to decisions that are made here tonight.
I'll be in accordance with your will and your plan.
That all may be passed by for our prayer in Christ's name.
Amen.
Brian, would you leave us a pledge, please?
I pledge allegiance to the light of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation under God.
Thank you.
Okay.
I am number four as public input and unscheduled personal appearances.
Anyone in the audience that wishes to address the council on any agenda items.
There being none out of fire's consent agenda staff recommends item 6 through 10 be placed on the consent agenda.
There are no objections or anything emotionally.
Most of you are approved, man.
Second, roll call, please.
Johnson.
All right.
Question.
I.
Forster.
I'm this.
I.
Chil.
And you have my agenda in.
There.
I got mine.
Okay.
I have a number.
Number 11 first national bank contractor process.
You tell any payment for the city of Miami, Jill.
Yes.
We have a second bank.
Thankfully that is going to allow or going to take payment.
You tell the payments for us.
Good.
So this works in well with our remodel that's going on right now.
We're hoping our plan is to be back into place no later than June 29th probably.
little before, but no later than 29. First national bank has three office locations and two
drivers, so that adds four drivers all together, which make a nice convenience. And if you
approve this contract tonight, they are going to start taking payments Wednesday the 15th.
Okay. And are the terms of this the same as with the other financial institution? Essentially yes.
Which is no charge of the tax credit. Correct. Outstanding. Good job. Okay. Do we need a motion?
I could I had one more thing very quickly. I'd like to one out. I think Jill and her staff did a
phenomenal job getting this set up. But when they were talking to different banks about this,
we were talking about terms and conditions. And the first bank that came in well state, they just
basically had terms and conditions that were just perfect. And we went with them. But the other banks
came back to us and basically, I think there was a little bit of a surprise because they thought we might
come back to them. And they indicated very much they wanted to be part of this and wanted to be
helping us with our community. So again, first national work very closely in getting this. I
think there's some other banks that are working on this as well. So we didn't mean to be shutting
anybody out because of our if for us, it's going to be terrific for us. And as I said, I think Jill and her
staff did a terrific job on that. A little bit of communication on that. So anyway, we got first national.
We hope we're going to have others coming in here too. So we're pretty happy about it. All right.
Thanks, Jill. I have a number 10, a proof fiscal year 2016 2017 budget in accordance with state
statute. Dean, did you have any comments on that? I know that's on the regular agenda. We were going to
talk a little bit about some changes. But, um, well, he's at just an extra budget here and here on the
council. It's not. So no, he's right. It's a total number 10. No, 10, which was part of consent.
So we're on 11. Yeah, we're on 11. Okay. Yeah. Which is the, we're on 11 12.
We need to vote for item 11. I make absolutely vote. Yes. She's made the motion. I make a motion.
You're second. I did. Okay. Good. I'm arrested. All right. The Western. Johnson.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm thankful they were on the item 12. New business, any new business? Anyone?
Being the new. I don't have this agenda now. That item 13 is staff reports, which are in your packet.
If there are no questions, I don't 14 is trust the community announcements any announcements under this item.
I have 15 is a German. Do we have a motion to a German? Make a motion? And a second.
That's the roll call. Forester. Hi. Johnson. All right. Western. Hi. Louis. Hi. Shult.
Hi. We're going to take just a moment before we move into our council meeting.